Guide to the Ken Kennedy academic records, 1967-2007 MS 206
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
- Series II: Committees, 1986-2007 (Boxes 17-39)
  - Subseries B: Non-Rice, 1987-2007
    - CRAY Form S-3 Registration Statement memorandum. 2003 January 7 (Box 30, Folder 5)
    - CRAY Public Offering prospectus memorandum. 2003 February 19 (Box 30, Folder 6)
    - CRAY Stock Option Agreement. 2003 June 27 (Box 30, Folder 7)
    - CRAY, Inc. SEC Elec Filing Number for Ken Kennedy. 2003 June 27 (Box 30, Folder 8)
    - CRAY S-8 Signature Page. 2003 August 7 (Box 30, Folder 9)
    - CRAY, Inc. 10-K Statement. March 2003 (Box 30, Folder 10)
    - CRAY Form 10-K. March 2004 (Box 30, Folder 11)
    - CRAY W-9 2004. 2004 October 13 (Box 30, Folder 12)
    - CRAY, Inc. Lock-Up Agreement. 2003 February 11 (Box 30, Folder 13)
    - CRAY, Inc. Special Meeting Consent. 2003 April 15 (Box 30, Folder 14)
    - Teleconference with Frank Lederman (CRAY BOD). 2004 June 16 (Box 30, Folder 15)
    - CRAY BOD Teleconference. 2004 August 17 (Box 30, Folder 16)
    - CRAY Teleconference. 2005 February 28 (Box 30, Folder 17)
    - CRAY Compensation Committee Teleconference. 2005 November 1 (Box 30, Folder 18)
    - CRAY Inc. Compensation Committee. 2004 (Box 30, Folder 19)
    - CRAY Inc. Compensation Committee. 20 July 2004 (Box 30, Folder 20)
    - CRAY Inc. Compensation Committee. 2005 January 25 (Box 30, Folder 21)
    - CRAY Inc. Compensation Committee. 19 October 2005 (Box 30, Folder 22)
    - CRAY Compensation Committee. 2006 August 8 (Box 30, Folder 23)
    - CRAY BOD Compensation - 2003 Rates. 2003 August 4 (Box 30, Folder 24)
    - Jim Rottsolk CRAY, Inc. Handouts for Board Meeting. 2000 November 1 (Box 30, Folder 25)
    - CRAY Board Consent. 2003 June 26 (Box 30, Folder 26)
    - CRAY Board Information 2003. 2003 August 5 (Box 30, Folder 27)
    - CRAY, Inc. Board of Directors Q4 2002 Conference Call. 2002 February 26 (Box 30, Folder 28)
    - CRAY, Inc. Board Packet. 2001 May 16 (Box 30, Folder 29)
    - CRAY, Inc. Board Packet. 2001 August 1 (Box 30, Folder 30)
    - CRAY, Inc. Board Packet. 2001 November 7 (Box 30, Folder 31)
    - CRAY, Inc. Board Packet. 2002 May 29 (Box 30, Folder 32)
    - CRAY BOARD of Directors Meeting Schedule 2003. 2002 December 5 (Box 30, Folder 33)
    - CRAY Board Meeting Schedule. 2005 April 29 (Box 30, Folder 34)
    - CRAY, Inc. BOD binder Memorandum. 2006 May 3 (Box 30, Folder 35)
    - CRAY, Inc. BOD Strategy Committee Meeting. 2006 August 8 (Box 30, Folder 36)
    - CRAY, Inc. Board of Directors. 2004 (Box 30, Folder 37)
    - CRAY, Inc. Board Roster. 2004 (Box 30, Folder 38)
    - CRAY, Inc. Board Meeting. 2000 May 31 (Box 30, Folder 39)
    - CRAY, Inc. Board Meeting. 2000 Aug 2 (Box 30, Folder 40)
    - CRAY, Inc. Board Meeting. 2002 July 31 (Box 30, Folder 41)
    - CRAY, Inc. Board Meeting. 2002 October 30 (Box 30, Folder 42)
    - CRAY, Inc. Board Meeting. 2003 February 5 (Box 30, Folder 43)
    - CRAY, Inc. Board Meeting. 2003 May 21 (Box 30, Folder 44)
    - CRAY, Inc. Board Meeting. 2003 July 30 (Box 30, Folder 45)
    - CRAY, Inc. Board Meeting. 2003 Oct 29 (Box 30, Folder 46)
    - CRAY, Inc. Board Meeting. 2004 January 28 (Box 30, Folder 47)
    - CRAY, Inc. Board Meeting. 2004 May 12 (Box 30, Folder 48)
    - CRAY, Inc. Board Meeting. 2004 July 21 (Box 30, Folder 49)
    - CRAY, Inc. Board Meeting. 2004 Oct 20 (Box 30, Folder 50)
    - CRAY, Inc. Board Meeting. 2005 January 26 (Box 31, Folder 1)
    - CRAY, Inc. Board Meeting. 2005 May 11 (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - CRAY, Inc. Board Meeting. 2005 July 19-20 (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - CRAY, Inc. Board Meeting. 2005 Oct 19 (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - CRAY, Inc. Board Meeting. 2006 February 15 (Box 31, Folder 5)
    - CRAY, Inc. Board Meeting. 2006 August 9 (Box 31, Folder 6)
    - Stellar Computer 1986 info (Box 31, Folder 7)
    - Stellar 25-26 Aug 1986 (Box 31, Folder 8)
    - Stellar correspondence 1987 (Box 31, Folder 9)
    - Stellar Graphics Supercomputer Model GS1000 System Overview. Nov 29 1987 (Box 31, Folder 10)
    - Stellar Computer Inc. Technical Advisory Board. Dec 7-8 1987 (Box 31, Folder 11)
    - Stellar TAB May 1988 (Box 31, Folder 12)
    - Stellar TAB Sept 1988 (Box 31, Folder 13)
    - Stellar Slipstream 12-13 March 1989 (Box 31, Folder 14)
    - Stellar 1986-1997 (Box 31, Folder 15)
    - Stellar Computer Inc. Technical Advisory Board Currency Architecture (Box 31, Folder 16)
    - Stellar Advisory Board Info (Box 31, Folder 17)
    - Stellar Agreement (Box 31, Folder 18)
    - Stellar Article and Performance Brief (Box 31, Folder 19)
    - Stellar Stock Info (Box 31, Folder 20)
    - Ken's Personal Stock in Stellar - Ardent, Inc. (Box 31, Folder 21)
    - Stellar/Stardent Companies Board of Directors (Box 31, Folder 22)
    - Stardent (General) (Box 31, Folder 23)
    - Stardent 1990 (Box 31, Folder 24)
    - RISC Performance Comparisons. 23 July 1987 (Box 31, Folder 25)
    - MIPS Computer Systems Performance Brief (Box 31, Folder 26)
    - Robelen Report (Box 31, Folder 27)
    - Belmont Computer (Box 31, Folder 28)
    - High-Performance Applications Requesting High-Speed Broadband Networks Proposals. 22-24 Jan 1996 (Box 31, Folder 29)
    - New Paradigms for Manufacturing Workshop. 2-4 May 1994 (Box 31, Folder 30)
    - National High-Performance Software Exchange (Box 31, Folder 31)
    - Computer and Computational Sciences Division Review. 2-4 May 2006 (Box 31, Folder 32)
    - Deloitte and Touche Technology CEO Summit. 11-13 May 2000 (Box 31, Folder 33)
    - NAE Reference Letter for Nomination of David Kuck. 1990 June 18 (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - NAE Reference Letter for Nomination of Niklaus Wirth. 1992 June 15 (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - NAE Reference Letter for Nomination of Steve Wallach. 1993 May 18 (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - NAE Reference Letter for Nomination of K. Mani Chandy. 1994 May 10 (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - NAE Reference Letter for Nomination of Mary Wheeler. 1994 June 15 (Box 32, Folder 5)
    - NAE Reference Letter for Nomination of Michael Harrison. 1994 June 16 (Box 32, Folder 6)
    - NAE Reference Letter for Nomination of Marc Auslander. 1994 June 16 (Box 32, Folder 7)
    - NAE Reference Letter for Nomination of Robert Ewald. 1996 June 12 (Box 32, Folder 8)
    - NAE Reference Letter for Nomination of Danny C. Sorensen. 2000 (Box 32, Folder 9)
    - NAE Reference Letter for Nomination of Peter Michael Kogge. 2000 June 6 (Box 32, Folder 10)
    - NAE Reference Letter for Nomination of Ivo Barbusica. 2000 June 6 (Box 32, Folder 11)
    - NAE Reference Letter for Nomination of Jeanne Ferrante. 2000 June 6 (Box 32, Folder 12)
    - NAE Reference Letters for Nomination of Sartaj Sahni 2001 (Box 32, Folder 13)
    - NAE Reference Letters for Nomination of John Dennis 2001 (Box 32, Folder 14)
    - NAE Reference Letter for Nomination of Lawrence H. Landweber. 2001 (Box 32, Folder 15)
    - NAE List of References for Burton Smith. May 2002 (Box 32, Folder 16)
    - NAE Reference Letter for Nomination of Irving Wladawsky-Berger. June 2002 (Box 32, Folder 17)
    - NAE Reference Letter for Nomination of W. Dale Compton. 2002 June 4.NAE (Box 32, Folder 18)
    - NAE Reference Letter for Nomination of Ian Foster. 2003 April 26 (Box 32, Folder 19)
    - NAE Reference Letter for Nomination of Paul Messina. May 2003 (Box 32, Folder 20)
    - NAE Reference Letters for Nomination of Hector Ruiz 2004 (Box 32, Folder 21)
    - NAE Reference Letter for Nomination of Fran Berman. 2004 May 27 (Box 32, Folder 22)
    - NAE Reference Letter for Nomination of Lennart Johnson. 2004 May 27 (Box 32, Folder 23)
    - NAE Reference Letters for Nomination of Dan Reed. June 2004 (Box 32, Folder 24)
    - NAE Reference Letters for Nomination of Cherri Pancake. June 2004 (Box 32, Folder 25)
    - NAE Reference Letter for Nomination of Ivo Barbusica. 2004 June 2 (Box 32, Folder 26)
    - NAE Reference Letters for Nomination of Sartaj Sahni 2005 (Box 32, Folder 27)
    - NAE Reference Letters for Nomination of Bill Gropp 2005 (Box 32, Folder 28)
    - NAE Updated Reference Letter for Nomination of Dan Reed. 2005 (Box 32, Folder 29)
    - NAE Reference Letters for Nomination of Josh Fisher 2005 (Box 32, Folder 30)
    - NAE Reference Letters for Nomination of John Dennis 2005 (Box 32, Folder 31)
    - NAE Reference Letters for Nomination of Uzi Vishkim. 2005 April 4 (Box 32, Folder 32)
    - NAE Reference Letter for Nomination of James Kahle. 2006 May 1 (Box 32, Folder 33)
    - NAE Nomination for Mary Wheeler. 1991 (Box 32, Folder 34)
    - NAE Nomination for Richard Tapia. 1991 (Box 32, Folder 35)
    - NAE Nomination for William Wulf. 1992 (Box 32, Folder 36)
    - NAE Nomination Form for Keith Uncapher 1994 (Box 32, Folder 37)
    - NAE Nomination for Larry Smarr. 1994 May 19 (Box 32, Folder 38)
    - NAE Nomination for Burton Smith. 1994-1996 (Box 32, Folder 39)
    - NAE Nomination for John Dennis. 1995 (Box 32, Folder 40)
    - NAE Nomination Form for Marwan Simaan. 1995 (Box 32, Folder 41)
    - Nomination Form for William Gates III. 1995 (Box 32, Folder 42)
    - NAE Nomination for Guy Steele. 1999 (Box 32, Folder 43)
    - NAE Nomination for Jayadev Misra. 1999 (Box 32, Folder 44)
    - NAE Nomination for Jack Schwartz. 1999-2000 (Box 32, Folder 45)
    - NAE Nomination for Jack Dongarra. 2000 (Box 32, Folder 46)
    - NAE Nomination for Sidney Karin 2000 (Box 32, Folder 47)
    - National Academy of Engineering Nomination - Fox, Geoffrey. 2001 (Box 32, Folder 48)
    - NAE Nomination for Moshi Vardi. 2001 (Box 32, Folder 49)
    - NAE Nomination for Burton Smith. 2002 (Box 32, Folder 50)
    - NAE Nomination for Sid Karin. 2004 (Box 32, Folder 51)
    - NAE Nomination for Andrew White. May 2004 (Box 32, Folder 52)
    - NAE Renomination of Cherri Pancake. March 2005 (Box 32, Folder 53)
    - NAE Renomination of Geoffrey Fox. 2005 (Box 32, Folder 54)
    - NAE Nomination for John Doerr. 2006 (Box 32, Folder 55)
    - NAE 2002-2003 Award Nomination Forms (Box 32, Folder 56)
    - NAE 2003 Election Renominations (Box 32, Folder 57)
    - NAE Nomination Letters. 2003 April 18 (Box 32, Folder 58)
    - NAE 2004 Final Nominations (Box 32, Folder 59)
    - NAE 2006 Nominations (Box 32, Folder 60)
    - NAE Award Nominations Booklet. 2005 January 4 (Box 32, Folder 61)
    - NAE 2002 Election Final Ballot (Box 32, Folder 62)
    - NAE Final Ballot 2003 Elections (Box 32, Folder 63)
    - NAE 2003 Officers and Councillors Election (Box 32, Folder 64)
    - NAE Ballot 2002 Officers (Box 32, Folder 65)
    - NAE 2004 Election Candidates (Box 32, Folder 66)
    - NAE 2004 Election Forms (Box 32, Folder 67)
    - NAE Awards 2003-2004 Call for Nominations (Box 32, Folder 68)
    - NAE Engineering Awards 2004-2005 Call for Nominations (Box 32, Folder 69)
    - NAE Call for Nominating Committee 2002 (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - NAE Elections 1994 (Box 33, Folder 2)
    - NAE Elections 1995 (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - NAE Officer Election. 2006 (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - NAE 2007 Election (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - NAE Policies and Procedures for Election. June 1990 (Box 33, Folder 6)
    - NAE 2003 Election Guidelines (Box 33, Folder 7)
    - NAE Candidate Comment Forms. 1994 (Box 33, Folder 8)
    - NAE Member Comments, 2000 Election (Box 33, Folder 9)
    - NAE 2002 Election Member Comments (Box 33, Folder 10)
    - NAE 2003 Election Member Comments (Box 33, Folder 11)
    - NAE 2004 Election Member Comments - Section 5 (Box 33, Folder 12)
    - NAE Articles of Organization and Bylaws. November 1985 (Box 33, Folder 13)
    - NAE Articles of Organization and Bylaws. 2004 (Box 33, Folder 14)
    - NAE Peer Committee Meetings. 1994 (Box 33, Folder 15)
    - NAE Peer Committee Forms. 1996 (Box 33, Folder 16)
    - NAE Membership Letter. 1990 February 12 (Box 33, Folder 17)
    - NAE Membership Letter and Card. 2005 October 5 (Box 33, Folder 18)
    - Letter from Harold Leibowitz, President-elect of National Academy of Engineering, to members of NAE. 1995 June 23 (Box 33, Folder 19)
    - NAE Letter Resigning from Committee on Membership. 1999 March 4 (Box 33, Folder 20)
    - NAE Miscellaneous Notes and Letters. 1995-2000 (Box 33, Folder 21)
    - The National Academy of Engineering Candidates. 1992 (Box 33, Folder 22)
    - NAE Conflict of Interest Statement. August 1993 (Box 33, Folder 23)
    - NAE Section Five Lists. 1994-1996 (Box 33, Folder 24)
    - NAE Website Access. 2001 February 20 (Box 33, Folder 25)
    - NAE Guidelines and Examples. 2001 (Box 33, Folder 26)
    - NAE Report of the President. 2002 (Box 33, Folder 27)
    - NAE 2006 Officer Reports (Box 33, Folder 28)
    - The Federal High Performance Computing Program. 1989 September 8 (Box 33, Folder 29)
    - High Performance Computing: Advanced Research Projects Agency Should Do More to Foster Program Goals, US General Accounting Office. May 1993 (Box 33, Folder 30)
    - First Consultative Meeting with Dr. Ken Kennedy and Dr. Sid Karin on the DoD HPC Modernization Program Agenda. 1994 March 2 (Box 33, Folder 31)
    - DoD High Performance Computing Modernization Program, Requirements Analysis. April 1994 (Box 33, Folder 32)
    - High Performance Computing and Communications, FY 1995 Implementation Plan. April 1994 (Box 33, Folder 33)
    - Department of Defense, High Performance Computing Modernization Program Advanced Planning Briefing to Industry. 1994 June 6 (Box 33, Folder 34)
    - High Performance Computing and Communications: Toward a National Information Infrastructure. 1994 (Box 33, Folder 35)
    - High Performance Computing and Communications: Technology for the National Information Infrastructure. 1994 (Box 33, Folder 36)
    - Presidential Advisory Committee for High Performance Computing and Communications, Information Technology, and the Next Generation Internet. 1998 February 17 (Box 33, Folder 37)
    - High Performance Computing Contributions to DoD Mission Success 1998. 1998 August 7 (Box 33, Folder 38)
    - White Paper on "The Ethical, Legal, and Social Implications of Information Technology in Institutional and Cultural Contexts and Information Technology Workforce Issues." PITAC 1999 (Box 33, Folder 39)
    - Presidential Information Technology Advisory Committee, Subcommittee on Transforming the Government, Report to the PITAC-Nearly Final Draft. 2000 May 17 (Box 33, Folder 40)
    - Emails regarding PITAC Meeting Dates. 2001 October 10 (Box 33, Folder 41)
    - "Women in Computing" article from Communications of the ACM. January 1995 (Box 33, Folder 42)
    - Testimony of Ken Kennedy before the Subcommittee on Communications of the U.S. Senate Committee on Commerce, Science, and Transportation. 1997 June 3 (Box 33, Folder 43)
    - Notice 99-08, 99-09, 99-10 - Office of Science Grant Program. 1999 (Box 33, Folder 44)
    - President's Information Technology Advisory Committee Meeting. 1998 November 4. (Folder 1) (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - President's Information Technology Advisory Committee Meeting. 1998 November 4. (Folder 2) (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - President's Information Technology Advisory Committee Meeting. 1999 February 17 (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - President's Information Technology Advisory Committee Meeting. 1999 September 2. (Folder 1) (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - President's Information Technology Advisory Committee Meeting. 1999 September 2. (Folder 2) (Box 34, Folder 5)
    - President's Information Technology Advisory Committee Meeting. 2000 February 25. (Folder 1) (Box 34, Folder 6)
    - President's Information Technology Advisory Committee Meeting. 2000 February 25. (Folder 2) (Box 34, Folder 7)
    - President's Information Technology Advisory Committee Meeting. 2000 May 18 (Box 34, Folder 8)
    - President's Information Technology Advisory Committee Meeting. 2000 September 20. (Folder 1) (Box 34, Folder 9)
    - President's Information Technology Advisory Committee Meeting. 2000 September 20. (Folder 2) (Box 34, Folder 10)
    - President's Information Technology Advisory Committee Meeting. 2001 February 7-8. (Folder 1) (Box 34, Folder 11)
    - President's Information Technology Advisory Committee Meeting. 2001 February 7-8. (Folder 2) (Box 34, Folder 12)
    - President's Information Technology Advisory Committee Meeting. 2001 May 10-11 (Box 34, Folder 13)
    - President's Information Technology Advisory Committee Meeting. 2001 September 24-25 (Box 34, Folder 14)
    - President's Information Technology Advisory Committee Meeting, Transforming Government Panel. 2000 February 24 (Box 34, Folder 15)
    - President's Information Technology Advisory Committee Meeting, National Security Panel. 2001 August 30 (Box 34, Folder 16)
    - President's Information Technology Advisory Committee Meeting, National Security Panel. 2001 September 24 (Box 34, Folder 17)
    - President's Information Technology Advisory Committee, Open Source Software Panel. 2000 February 24 (Box 34, Folder 18)
    - President's Information Technology Advisory Committee, Software Subcommittee Meeting. 2001 September 24 (Box 34, Folder 19)
    - Advisory Committee on High Performance Computing and Communications, Information Technology, and the Next Generation Internet. 1997 February 27-28. (Folder 1) (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - Advisory Committee on High Performance Computing and Communications, Information Technology, and the Next Generation Internet. 1997 February 27-28. (Folder 2) (Box 35, Folder 2)
    - Advisory Committee on High Performance Computing and Communications, Information Technology, and the Next Generation Internet. 1997 June 24-25. (Folder 1) (Box 35, Folder 3)
    - Advisory Committee on High Performance Computing and Communications, Information Technology, and the Next Generation Internet. 1997 June 24-25. (Folder 2) (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - Advisory Committee on High Performance Computing and Communications, Information Technology, and the Next Generation Internet. 1997 December 9-10. (Folder 1) (Box 35, Folder 5)
    - Advisory Committee on High Performance Computing and Communications, Information Technology, and the Next Generation Internet. 1998 March 11. (Folder 1) (Box 35, Folder 6)
    - Advisory Committee on High Performance Computing and Communications, Information Technology, and the Next Generation Internet. 1998 March 11. (Folder 2) (Box 33, Folder 7)
    - Advisory Committee on High Performance Computing and Communications, Information Technology, and the Next Generation Internet. 1998 May 19. (Folder 1) (Box 35, Folder 8)
    - Advisory Committee on High Performance Computing and Communications, Information Technology, and the Next Generation Internet. 1998 May 19. (Folder 2) (Box 35, Folder 9)
    - PITAC High End. October 1997 (Box 35, Folder 10)
    - PITAC Report. 1998 March 8 (Box 35, Folder 11)
    - Background Information for Review of IT Initiative Option Papers, PITAC. 1998 October 14 (Box 35, Folder 12)
    - Final PITAC Report. 1999 March 19 (Box 35, Folder 13)
    - PITAC NSP Docs. 2000 (Box 35, Folder 14)
    - PITAC NSP Notes. 2000-2001 (Box 35, Folder 15)
    - PITAC NSP Draft. 2001 October 2. Due 2001 October 3 evening to NSP Panel (Box 35, Folder 16)
    - PITAC NSP Draft and Comments. 2001 October 8 (Box 35, Folder 17)
    - PITAC NSP Draft. 2002 February 19 (Box 35, Folder 18)
    - PITAC NSP Draft Report. 2002 February 28 (Box 35, Folder 19)
    - President's Information Technology Advisory Committee, Interim Report to the President. August 1998 (Box 35, Folder 20)
    - President's Committee of Advisors on Science and Technology Meeting. 1999 February 22 (Box 35, Folder 21)
    - Report to the President on the Use of Technology to Strengthen K-12 Education in the United States. March 1997 (Box 35, Folder 22)
    - Information Technology: Department of Energy Does Not Effectively Manage Its Supercomputers, US General Accounting Office. July 1998 (Box 35, Folder 23)
    - Networked Computing for the 21st Century, Supplement to the President's FY 1999 Budget. 1998 August 3 (Box 35, Folder 24)
    - White House HPCC Advisory Committee Letter. 1996 December 20 (Box 35, Folder 25)
    - Letter from John Bennett, US Department of the Interior. 1998 March 27 (Box 35, Folder 26)
    - Letter from Paul Smith, Department of Energy, Office of Defense Programs. September 1998 (Box 35, Folder 27)
    - Letter to Nick Smith, Chair of Subcommittee on Basic Research, regarding Congressional Testimony. 1999 April 28 (Box 35, Folder 28)
    - Testimony of Ken Kennedy to the Subcommittee on Basic Research on the U.S. House of Representatives, Committee on Science. 1999 March 16 (Box 35, Folder 29)
    - Testimony of Ken Kennedy before the Subcommittee on Science, Research, and Technology of the Committee on Science, Space, and Technology, U.S. House of Representatives. 1990 March 15 (Box 36, Folder 1)
    - High Performance Computing and Communications Advisory Committee Composition.1990 July 25 (Box 36, Folder 2)
    - High Performance Computing Initiative (White House Committee). 1990 (Box 36, Folder 3)
    - High Performance Computing Budgets Notes. Ca. 1991 (Box 36, Folder 4)
    - High Performance Computing and Communications Advisory Committee Meeting Notes. 1991 March 11 (Box 36, Folder 5)
    - High Performance Computing and Communications Advisory Committee Notes. 1991 March 15 (Box 36, Folder 6)
    - Seeking Solutions: High Performance Computing for Science, Background Paper"Congress of the U.S. Office of Technology Assessment. April 1991 (Box 36, Folder 7)
    - Computing Research Association letter to members regarding High Performance Computing Legislation. 1991 April 5 (Box 36, Folder 8)
    - Letter from John Rollwagen, CRAY Inc. to HPCCI Advisory Council regarding EEC Working Group on High Performance Computing, Commission of the European Communities. 1991 April 17 (Box 36, Folder 9)
    - Letter from D. Allan Bromley about PCAST Panel on High Performance Computing and Communications. 1991 August 12 (Box 36, Folder 10)
    - Letter to Allan Bromley of PCAST, accepting invitation as an expert on PCAST panel on High Performance Computing and Communications. 1991 August 27 (Box 36, Folder 11)
    - President's Council of Advisors on Science and Technology (PCAST) High Performance Computing and Communications Panel Report. March 1992 (Box 36, Folder 12)
    - High Performance Computing: Advanced Research Projects Agency Should Do More to Foster Program Goals, US Government Accountability Office. May 1993 (Box 36, Folder 13)
    - The High Performance Computing and Communications Program Hearing before the Subcommittee on Basic Research, Committee on Science. U.S. House of Reps. 1995 Oct. 31 (Box 36, Folder 14)
    - Advisory Committee for High Performance Computing and Communications, Information Technology, and the Next Generation Internet Roster. 1997 March 11 (Box 36, Folder 15)
    - President Bill Clinton's Letter to Ken Kennedy and Bill Joy regarding the President's Information Technology Advisory Committee Interim Report. 1998 August 10 (Box 36, Folder 16)
    - Letter from Eugene Wong, Executive Office of the President. Office of Science and Technology Policy, to Ken Kennedy. 1990 June 29 (Box 36, Folder 17)
    - U.S. Technological Policy, Executive Office of the President, Office of Science and Technological Policy. 1990 September 26 (Box 36, Folder 18)
    - Office of Technology Assessment Workshop/Paper Review. 1990 November 27 (Box 36, Folder 19)
    - Office of Technology Assessment Background Paper on the Commercialization of Flat Panel Displays. 1995 April 4 (Box 36, Folder 20)
    - Office of Technology Assessment Study: Innovation and Commercialization of Emerging Technologies Draft Review. 1995 August 17 (Box 36, Folder 21)
    - Office of Technology Assessment Report: Innovation and Commercialization of Emerging Technologies. September 1995 (Box 36, Folder 22)